businessreport.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy Policy - Baton Rouge Business Report

This Privacy Policy may be modified from time to time; the date of the most recent revisions will appear on this page. Check back often, as continued access of the website by you will constitute your acceptance of any revisions to the Privacy Policy.

Safeguarding the privacy of your information is very important to us. Louisiana Business Inc. does not sell, rent, give away or loan any personally identifiable information that we receive or gather with advertisers, third parties or individuals except in situations requiring us to by law or with user consent. We may share aggregate or summary information regarding our registered users with advertisers, third parties or individuals.

Online, or through other means of contact, when you subscribe, register, make purchases, submit surveys or at other times, we collect and store personally identifiable information from you that may include your name; your postal and email addresses; facts about your profession, company and responsibilities; and information regarding your computer system that may be passed on to an approved third party for storage and payment processing. All payment information is processed and stored by an authorized, PCI-compliant, third-party payment company. Partial credit card information may be securely stored for audit purposes. Approved third parties include: Authorize.net, Data Joe, Newzware, MailChimp, AdMate, SageCRM, Voter Voice, Saxotech, OnSwipe, Wufoo, Doubleclick, Unbounce and Disqus. This list is subject to change. Please contact us for an updated list or with questions regarding the information shared with these third parties.

Information collected about subscribers and users may be used by us and our affiliates to provide subscribers and users with the features of the site, to enable us to provide the products you requested, to personalize content and advertising, to send you email notifications about our services and products, for audits, to perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure interest in the various areas of our site (such as for product development purposes), to enforce our user agreement, and to inform advertisers as to how many users have seen or “clicked” their advertising banners. We will disclose site usage information to third parties only in aggregate.

For each visitor to this website, our Web server may automatically attempt to identify the user through a cookie set within your browser. This is done to provide access to the site.

If you do not want to receive email from us in the future, please update your subscription preferences [here](http://businessreport.com/section/enewsletters).

If you supply us with your telephone number and postal address online you may receive periodic mailings from us with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mailings, please email [circulation@businessreport.com](mailto:circulation@businessreport.com?subject=Privacy%20policy) and be sure to specify the contact information you would like removed from our list.

From time to time, we may use customer information for new, unanticipated purposes not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future, we will post the policy changes to our website to notify you of these changes.

With respect to security: When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we redirect visitors to a secure server. Visitors may verify their security status by looking for the “https://” portion of the URL in their browser or by calling us to verify the safety of their information.

If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at (225) 928-1700 or through the options listed on the [Contact Us](http://businessreport.com/section/businessreport1002) page.
